Office of the Vice President for Business and Finance records, 1950-ongoing UA.10.01.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2011-0006, circa 1960s-1992; 7.5 Linear Feet; 5 boxes
  - Federally Mandated Prog. - Cost to University (Box 53)
  - Governor of North Carolina (Box 53)
  - Human Resources Director Johnson (3 folders) (Box 53)
  - Traffic and Parking (Box 54)
  - Speeches (Box 54)
  - Report to the Board of Trustees (Box 54)
  - Motivation (Box 54)
  - Former Personnel Director R.S. Jackson (Box 54)
  - Chancellor (Brodie) (Box 54)
  - Duke University Athletic Association Budget (Box 54)
  - Loose Material 1 (Box 54)
  - Loose Material 2 (Box 54)
  - Loose Material 3 (Box 54)
  - Loose Material 4 (Box 54)
  - Payroll (Box 54)
  - Loose Material 5 (Box 54)
  - Loose Material 6 (Box 54)
  - Planning Reports (Box 54)
  - Loose Material 7 (Box 54)
  - Long Range Planning (Box 54)
  - Loose Material 8 (Box 54)
  - Flowers Drive Failure (Box 54)
  - Loose Material 9 (Box 54)
  - Heating Plant Task Force Report (Box 54)
  - CBH Report File, November 7, 1978 (Box 54)
  - Loose Material 10 (Box 54)
  - Loose Material 11 (Box 54)
  - Correspondence 1 (Box 54)
  - American Dream, Dream Arena (Box 54)
  - Loose Material 12 (Box 55)
  - Techspan Buisness Plans (Box 55)
  - Financial Reports (Box 55)
  - Whitford (Box 55)
  - Correspondence 2 (Box 55)
  - 10/3/82-5/8/83 (Box 55)
  - Correspondence 3 (Box 55)
  - Correspondence 4 (Box 55)
  - Correspondence 5 (Box 55)
  - Division of Marine Fisheries Re-Organization Evaluation, 1986 (Box 55)
  - Insurance Correspondence (Box 55)
  - Auxiliary Services Division Report (Box 55)
  - Business and Finance Division, Fiscal Year 1983/1984 Acutal vs. Budget, Plant and Other Fund Balances, Growth Analysis, Work Load Indicators (2 folders) (Box 55)
  - Resource Material (Box 55)
  - Duke University Marine Lab - Aquanautics (Box 55)
  - Public Safety (Box 55)
  - Hotel (Box 55)
  - Duke University Buisiness and Finance Committee Operations Through November 4, 1984, Fiscal Year 1985/1986 Forecast (Box 55)
  - 1984-1985 Annual Report (Box 55)
  - Duke University Business and Finance Committee, Operations for the Year Ending June 30, 1985 and Other Agenda Items, September 27, 1985 (Box 55)
  - Duke University Buisness and Finance Committee Operations Through March 31, 1985, Fiscal Year 1985/1986 Budget Proposal (Box 56)
  - Presentation Outline, Central Heating Plant Evaluation Study (Box 56)
  - Central Heating Plant Evaluation Study (Box 56)
  - Central Heating Plant Data Tabulations (Box 56)
  - The Division of Business and Finance Self-Study (Box 56)
  - Moving Forward, Business Division Staff Year Review and Goals, 1968 (Box 56)
  - Trustee Committee on Intercollegiate Athletics -- RESTRICTED (Box 56)
  - Confidential File (Box 56)
  - Personal Files, Correspondence, F-J, 1966-1975 (2 folders) (Box 56)
  - Cost Reduction Ideas in Business and Finance (Box 56)
  - Loose Material 13, circa 1992 (Box 56)
  - Personal Files, Correspondence, A-E, 1970-1975 (Box 56)
  - Personal Files, Correspondence, P-T, 1966-1975 (2 folders) (Box 56)
  - Personal Files, Correspondence, K-O, 1966-1975 (Box 56)
  - Personal Files, Correspondence, A-E, 1966-1969 (2 folders) (Box 56)
  - Secretarial Planner, 1969 (Box 56)
  - Executive Planner, 1967 (Box 56)
  - Executive Planner, 1968 (Box 56)
  - Executive Planner, 1985 (2 folders) (Box 56)
  - Duke Medical Center Employee Union Representation Cards (Box 56)
  - Nixon Library, 1981 (Box 56)
- Accession UA2012-0003, 2 boxes
  - Athletics, 1976-1979 (including Mike McGee) (Box 57)
  - Business and Finance, 1979 (Box 57)
  - Duke and Durham, 1975, 1979 (Box 57)
  - Faculty, 1976-1979 (Box 57)
  - Governmental Interference, 1975-1977 (4 folders) (Box 57)
  - Miscellaneous, 1977-1978 (Box 57)
  - Kenneth Pye, undated (Box 57)
  - Oliver Harvey, 1979 (Box 57)
  - Flyer: March to Avenge the Communist Workers Party Five, undated (Box 57)
  - Race Relations, 1977 (Box 57)
  - Security, 1961, 1977-1979 (Box 57)
  - Students, undated (Box 57)
  - Unions, 1977-1979 (Box 57)
  - University Center, 1979 (Box 58)
  - Vigil, 1968 (Box 58)
  - Salary Data, 1979-1980 (Box 58)
  - Long-Range Planning Committee, 1979 (Box 58)
  - General Appendices (including Registrar), 1979 (Box 58)
  - Appendices: Dept. of Education, 1979 (Box 58)
  - Appendices: Marine Laboratory, 1979 (Box 58)
  - Appendices: School of Nursing, 1979 (Box 58)
  - Appendices: Dept. of Sociology, 1979 (Box 58)
  - Appendices: School of Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1979 (2 folders) (Box 58)
- Accession UA2014.0083, 1970s-1984; 19 Linear Feet; 19 linear feet, 15 boxes. Some materials not foldered.
  Scope and Contents
  This accession consists of Charles Huestis's files, including correspondence, meeting minutes, reports, and other materials. There is significant material related to the Medical Center.
- Accession UA2017.0081, 1980; 1986; 2016; 1 Files
  - Accession UA2017.0081, correspondence, 1980; 1986; 2016 (Box 59)
    Includes a letter from Tom Butters to Chuck Huestis. Also included are copies of correspondence to members of the Duke Blue Devils Basketball team following their 72-69 point loss to Louisville in the National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA) Finals in 1986 (Weldon H. Williams; Mark Alarie; H. Tommy Amaker; David M. Henderson; Johnny E. Dawkins, Jr.; Jay Bilas; and coach Mike Krzyzewski).